ZAK MONNET

Nashville, TN 37207

Phone: 615-496-0462 | Email: zakmonnet@gmail.com

LinkedIn: www.linkedin.com/in/zakmonnet | GitHub: http://github.com/outoftune266 | Portfolio:

https://outoftune266.github.io/

SUMMARY

Full Stack Web Developer with a background in Music. I am a creative person with a passion for knowledge and learning. I am solution-oriented, using my creativity to effectively solve problems. I am an experienced team leader with effective communication skills that inspire and motivate my teams.

TECHNICAL SKILLS

Languages/Technologies: HTML, CSS, Javascript, React, Node, Express, MySQL, MongoDB Applications: Logic/Garageband, Finale

PROJECTS

K.I.T. - Keep In Touch | https://github.com/Andrea-Boyd/Project-3 | https://sheltered-plains-45359.herokuapp.com/

- Close group messaging app with real time functionality
- Built real time Web Socket and backend server/database logic
- HTML, CSS, Javascript, React, JSX, Socket.io

Time Zone Traveler | https://github.com/outoftune266/05-Work-Day-Scheduler/ | https://outoftune266.github.io/05-Work-Day-Scheduler/

- Travel planning tool to find and add points of interest to visit
- Built map functionality, collaborated on database logic and design
- HTML, CSS, Javascript, JQuery, MySQL, Foundations

Song Scout | https://github.com/outoftune266/Song-Scout/ | https://outoftune266.github.io/Song-Scout/

- Easy to use tool to learn more about your favorite artists and albums
- Built logic to retrieve album data and song lyrics
- Created Show/Hide functionality so application runs in one HTML file
- HTML, CSS, Javascript, JQuery, Bootstrap

Weather Dashboard | https://github.com/outoftune266/06-Weather-Dashboard | https://outoftune266.github.io/06-Weather-Dashboard

- Tool to view current and 5-day forecast weather data
- Designed and built myself
- HTML, CSS, Javascript, JQuery, Bootstrap

Work Day Scheduler | https://github.com/outoftune266/05-Work-Day-Scheduler/ | https://outoftune266.github.io/05-Work-Day-Scheduler/

- Simple tool to plan daily tasks by hour
- Designed and built myself
- HTML, CSS, Javascript, JQuery, Moment.js, Bootstrap

EXPERIENCE

Logistics Broker 2018 – 2020

Universal Capacity Solutions

Antioch, TN

Worked as a member of brokerage team to create shipping solutions for our customers *Key Accomplishments:*

• Set one week company sales company record with brokerage team - January 2019

Contract Game Soundtrack Composer Space Inch, LLC

2016

Nashville, TN

Composed and recorded music for mobile game "Cookie Pop" Key Accomplishments:

• Worked closely with developer to create music sync/repeat functionality

Fundraising Committee Chair/Board Member Radio Free Nashville

2015 – Present

Nashville, TN

Organized multiple fundraising events each year, raising over \$28,000 *Key Accomplishments:*

- Managed team of volunteers for planning and execution
- Managed on-site event logistics

Senior Hardlines Team Leader Target Corporation

2009 - 2018

Nashville, TN

Leader on Duty/Key Carrier that worked to develop talent for performance and promotion *Key Accomplishments:*

- Drove successive year to year sales increases above 4%
- Project Team Leader for 2015 Innovation Remodel
- Launched Craft/Local Beer Program

EDUCATION

Bootcamp Certificate: Vanderbilt University, Nashville, TN

A 24-week intensive program focused on gaining technical programming skills in HTML5, CSS3, Javascript, JQuery, Bootstrap, Firebase, Node Js, MySQL, MongoDB, Express, Handelbars.js & ReactJS.

Bachelor of Music, Commercial Piano and Composition: Belmont University, Nashville, TN Emphasis in composition and arranging